翻译: 张有才 Amber Melanie
嘿 Jake 过来帮我看一下好吗
Hey Jake, can I show you something over here?
没问题 哥们儿
Sure thing, bud.
我想给Genevieve发一张性感照片
I'm trying to send Genevieve a sexy pic.
这么看我屁屁翘吗
Does this make my bubble butt pop?
校对: 番茄滚滚
算了 我后悔了
Nope. I'm out.
后期: Nico
- 这谁  - 不知道
- Who's that? - I don't know.
呃 不好意思 这是我的办公桌
Um, excuse me, pal. Think you're at my desk.
压制: 怪查理
喔喔喔
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
放下 放下武器
Drop it! Drop the weapon!
别做傻事
Don't be a dum-dum.
同志们 这是Adrian Pimento警探
Squad, meet Detective Adrian Pimento.
他深入潜伏了十二年
He's been deep undercover for the last 12 years,
最近刚刚结束 现在要回到99片区
but he's just resurfaced, and he's rejoining the Nine-Nine.
简   直
That...is...
棒呆
awesome!
神烦警探
第三季 第十七集
电波诚译
你们中有的人是刚刚第一次见Pimento警探
Some of you just met Detective Pimento,
有的则在他去卧底前就认识他了
and, of course, some of you knew him before he went undercover.
Hitchcock和Scully 你俩居然还在这儿工作
Hitchcock and Scully. Ha. You guys still work here?
他们摆脱我们的唯一方式就是把我们装进运尸袋
The only way they're getting rid of us is in a body bag.
其实他们真装过一次 但那次只是虚惊一场
It actually happened once, but it was a false alarm.
Pimento警探会回到他原来的办公桌工作
Detective Pimento will be returning to his old desk.
Peralta暂时搬去休息室
Peralta will temporarily be moved to the break room.
有问题吗
Questions?
你卧底的时候是干什么的
What'd you do undercover?
我替 "屠夫" Jimmy Figgis干活
I worked for Jimmy "The Butcher" Figgis.
他可是A级犯罪团伙成员 把那里的一切都告诉我
That is an A-list mobster. Tell me literally everything.
所有人都闭嘴
Everyone, shut up!
我基本上就是替他收钱
Pretty much just a bagman for him.
不过 也干点别的啦
I mean, I did some other stuff.
我们一般都会讲搞笑的事儿
Um, we usually try to tell funnier little stories.
但是我替屠夫做的事一点都不搞笑
Well, there's nothing funny about what I did for The Butcher.
我必须要学会不眨眼
I've had to learn not to blink,
因为每次我一闭眼 我眼前都是一片恐怖景象
because every time I close my eyes, I see a fresh horror.
哇哦 重口
Ooh, dark.
可是你怎么能保持眼睛湿润呢
But how do you keep your eyes moist?
其实关于保持眼睛湿润
Actually, I have a very funny story about
我有一个很好笑的故事
keeping my eyes moist.
很搞笑吧
Come on...
并没有
Nope.
还是没懂你的笑点
Still not getting that vibe, man.
- 真的吗  - 嗯嗯
- Really? - Mm-mm.
我会继续努力的 同志们 是我的错
I'll get there. That's my bad, everybody.
解散
Dismissed.
长官
Sir,
我可以让Pimento跟我一起跟进破门侵入案吗
can I partner with Pimento on my B&E?
他真的棒呆了
That guy is awesome.
他简直就是现实版的<忠奸人>
He's like a real life Donnie Brasco.
<忠奸人>不是结局很惨吗
Isn't Donnie Brasco a really sad movie that ends terribly?
对 但是他有那件很酷的夹克
Yeah, but he's got that cool jacket,
而且总是在码头
and he's always down at the docks.
我不确定我想不想让你跟Pimento一起工作
I'm not sure I want you working with Pimento.
他有点情绪不稳定
He's a little unstable.
破机器
Machine!
在他的心理上 这是一个艰难的过渡期
Psychologically, this could be a very difficult transition.
我懂的 我也做了63天卧底
Yeah, I know, I went undercover.
没什么大不了的 你可能忘了
63 days, no big deal. You probably forgot.
怎么可能忘得了这就是你的语音信箱留言
No, it's your outgoing voice mail message.
嘿 我是Jake
Hey, it's Jake.
暂时不能接电话
Can't get to the phone right now.
我可能又要去卧底了 就像上次去卧底了63天一样
I might be undercover again, like I was for 63 days.
拜拜
Bye!
听着 我知道他现在在经历什么
Look, I know what he's going through.
让我来引领他走出黑暗吧
Let me be the man that brings him in from the cold.
好吧 他可以和你一起跟进破门侵入案
All right, he can work the B&E with you.
但是你一定要淡定
Just make sure you take it easy.
呃 长官 我今早迟到了20分钟
Uh, sir, I was 20 minutes late for work today.
你用不着提醒我要淡定
I don't think you need to tell me about taking it easy.
你是在吹嘘自己是一个不称职的员工吗
Are you bragging about being a bad employee?
不是
No.
解散了我
Dismissed? Me?
我想出了一个好方法来
I figured out the best way
欢迎Pimento重回99区
to welcome Pimento to the Nine-Nine.
不要碍他的事 或许可以请他喝东西
Stay out of his way, maybe buy him a drink,
但是不要做奇怪的事
not do anything weird?
我正在给他炖山羊肉
I'm making him a goat stew.
呃 好吧
Huh...all right.
这是一道土库曼斯坦传统菜
Yeah, now, this Turkmenistani dish
里面的肉用的是那种肥到站不起来的
is traditionally made from an animal that's been so overfed
山羊身上的
it can no longer stand.
简直是我的梦想啊
That's the dream.
这些都是有根据的
Everything is authentic.
我甚至还从土库曼斯坦
I even ordered the pressure cooker
订了一个高压锅
from Turkmenistan.
所以你现在上了恐怖分子监视名单咯
So you're on a terrorist watch list now?
没错 国土安全局的人已经去过我家了
Oh, yeah, Homeland Security's been in my house, yep.
现在 只需要再炖11个小时32分钟
Now, this just needs to cook for another 11 hours, 32 minutes,
再加6
and 6--
搞什么鬼 Boyle 你差点杀了我
What the hell, Boyle! You almost killed me!
我才不要在炖羊肉事故中挂掉
I'm not going out in a stew-making accident!
Terry要为总统护驾而死
Terry's gonna die saving the President,
不然老子就要永生不死
or Terry's never gonna die!
我们不可能自己把这里打扫干净
There's no way we can clean this up by ourselves.
我们需要帮助
We're gonna need help.
不不不不不
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
你什么意思
What are you saying?
你知道她什么意思
You know what she's saying, man.
噢 不
Oh, no.
要去找刻薄Marge了
Mean Marge.
所以每次你的小肥指头一打响指
So we're supposed to come running to clean up your mess
我们都得跑去给你收拾烂摊子吗
every time you snap your fat little fingers?
不不  其实我不会打响指
Oh, no, no, I actually can't snap my fingers,
因为我的指头一直都很湿
they're always too wet.
我觉得 因为这是你们的工作
And I just thought, since it's your job--
我懂了
Oh, I see.
你们这些警察都认为自己逼格高所以不用打扫是吧
You cops think you're too good to clean up after yourselves?
不是 我可以自己打扫 我会
Uh--no, I can do it myself, I'll just--
这是工会的工作
That's union work!
你好大的胆子居然敢抢我们的工作
How dare you try to steal our jobs.
那我们下一步怎么办
So where do we go from here?
有句谚语说得好
Well, you know the old saying,
"通厕所的最好办法就是让它堵着吧"
"The only way to unclog a toilet is to let it sit."
你是清洁人员 你知道这是不对的吧
You're a janitor. You should know that's not true.
伙计们 去把垃圾倒了
Boys, take out the trash.
太棒了 所以你会帮我们清理啦
Oh, great! So you will do it?
噢 我就是垃圾 我懂了
Oh! I'm the trash, I get it.
难怪你的语气是那样
Okay, that makes more sense with your tone.
哎呀 爱你哦 Marge
Oops! Oh... Love you, Marge.
长官 你要见我
You wanted to see me, sir?
对 我有一个特殊任务给你
Yes, I have a special project for you.
好哒 不过我得跟你说
Okay, but I'll have you know right now
我只坐头等舱
I only fly first class.
并没有要你坐飞机去哪儿的意思
I'm not flying you anywhere.
我向M.C. Guffin基金会申请
I made an application to the M.C. Guffin Foundation
拨款来升级我们办公室的设备
for a grant to upgrade our office equipment.
不幸的是他们要求提交一个视频
Unfortunately, they require a video submission.
我知道你之前有过视频制作的经历
I understand you have some filmmaking experience.
那必须 我的视频在Vine上可是被卡戴珊弟弟转发过的
Well, you know, I've been re-Vined by Rob Kardashian,
Vine是一个6秒短视频服务网站
所以 是的 我是个导演
so, yeah, I'm a director.
这是我的想法
Here's what I'm picturing:
我以费里尼风格的装束入场
I enter, in, like, a Fellini-style getup.
Rosa则打扮成豪猪
Rosa's dressed like a porcupine--
不不 我们一切从简
Oh, no, no. We're just gonna do a simple,
直接展示一下我们片区
straightforward tour of the precinct
我和Diaz警探主演
featuring Detective Diaz and me.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
你们俩的荧幕形象都不是很有活力啊
You're not our most dynamic screen presences.
我可以很有活力
I can be dynamic.
感叹号
Exclamation point.
Diaz和我很有默契
Well, Diaz and I have that kind of easy chemistry
- 我们可以补充完对方的  - 话
- where we finish each other's - Sentences.
请不要打断我
Please, don't interrupt me.
这种无稽之谈是不会出现在镜头上的
That kind of nonsense won't happen on camera.
嘿 嘿 Pimento
Hey, hey, Pimento.
嘿
Hey!
这是我的办工桌 懂了吗
This is my desk, okay?
好吧 这种打招呼的方式有点不同寻常
Okay, well, now that that's out of the way,
我只是来告诉你
I was just coming to let you know
我们会一起跟进一桩破门侵入案
we're gonna work a B&E together;
我们要成为搭档了
we're gonna be partners.
不 我都是单独行动的
Nope. I work alone.
而且"屠夫"说过他在纽约警局有间谍
Plus, The Butcher says he has spies in the NYPD,
所以我不会相信这里的娘炮
so I trust none of these dildos.
听着 你可以信任我
Listen, you can trust me.
- 哥迷恋你  - 好吧
- I'm, like, obsessed with you. - Fine.
告诉我一件你从未告诉过别人的秘密
Tell me something you've never told another living soul.
呃
Um...
噢 有一个
Ooh, here's one.
我举不起饮水机的水桶
I'm actually not strong enough to lift a water cooler jug,
所以我总是想方设法地让Terry举
so I always find a way to make Terry do it.
我也有一个秘密
Here's mine.
"屠夫" Jimmy曾经让我把槌球的门
Jimmy "The Butcher" Made me drive a croquet wicket
从一个人的眼睛那里穿进大脑里
through a guy's eyes into his brain.
他的脑浆从眼睛里流出来 就像在流眼泪一样
Brain leaked out his eyes like he was crying his own mind.
我的天哪
My goodness.
听过你的秘密以后
Now that I've heard yours,
我觉得我应该把我举不起饮水机水桶
I feel like my water cooler thing
这件事编的更有料一点的 但是
could have been a little more juicy, but...
不 那样对你来说才是尴尬
No. That was embarrassing for you.
你现在就是我兄弟了
A bond has been made.
能够再次信任别人的感觉真好 兄弟
Feels good to trust again, brother.
哇哦 你要么是个半机械人
Wow, either you are a cyborg
要么就是你这衣服里装的武器太多了
or you're carrying so many weapons in this jacket.
嘿 去厨房 现在
Hey. Kitchen, now.
好的
Okay.
怎么了
What's up?
那家伙不太对劲
Something's not right about that guy.
为啥 就因为他一直在片区里
Why, just because he keeps threatening to kill me
威胁要弄死我 拜托 成熟一点好吗
in the middle of a police precinct? Uh, grow up.
因为我居然对他有性趣
Because I'm physically attracted to him.
这难道是件坏事
And that's bad?
我只对变态有性趣 比如 "秃鹫"  ShamWow广告代言人
I'm only attracted to creeps: the Vulture, the ShamWow guy,
我小的时候
and when I was a kid,
还特别喜欢小魔怪里的邪恶精灵
I had a major crush on the evil Gremlin.
你指Stripe 你疯了吗
Stripe? Are you crazy?
对 反正我不会和善良小精灵Gizmo上床
Yeah, well I'm not gonna bone Gizmo.
- 我就会  - 小心点Pimento
- I would. - Careful with Pimento.
不会有事的
It's gonna be fine.
你好啊搭档
Hey, partner.
我一直在等你
I've been waiting for you.
如果吓到你了我很抱歉
Sorry if I surprised you.
只是我做卧底时 只有在半夜的时候
It's just when I was undercover, the middle of the night
我才可以做警察的工作
was the only time I could do actual police work.
你是怎么进来的
Uh, how'd you get in the apartment?
哦 很简单
Oh, it was easy.
我勾引了楼上的老太太
I just seduced the old lady upstairs,
从防火梯那里下来 然后撬开了窗户
came down the fire escape, jimmied the window open.
呯嗙嘭 我就进来了
Bing-bang-boom, I'm inside your living quarters.
确实是
Totally.
当然 下次你可以给我打个电话 你知道的
Course, next time you could just give me a call, you know.
拜访朋友有两种方法
Two ways to pop in on a friend.
我没杀掉楼上的老太太
I didn't kill the old lady upstairs,
如果你是担心这个的话
if that's what you're worried about.
好吧 我现在担心了
Well, I am now.
噢 等一下
Oh, wait a minute.
你觉得我很奇怪
You think I'm being weird.
天啊 我不应该来的 这是你的公寓
Oh, I shouldn't have come here. This is your apartment.
我太抱歉了Jake Paul你真蠢
I'm so sorry, Jake! Stupid, Paul!
笨蛋 你个白痴 Paul
Stupid! You idiot, Paul!
- 嘿 Pimento  - 啊
- Hey! Pimento! - Huh?!
- Paul是谁  - 哇哦
- Who's Paul? - Whoa.
Paul Sneed是我卧底时的名字
Paul Sneed was my undercover name.
好吧 妈的 Jake
'Kay? Damn it, Jake.
我再也不知道我是谁了
I don't know who I am anymore.
你卧底时候能随意选名字
You could have chose any name to go undercover,
结果你选了Paul Sneed吗
and you picked Paul Sneed?
听起来挺疯狂的
Seems kind of crazy.
我不该来的
I shouldn't have come here.
这是一个错误 我还没准备好
This was a mistake. I'm not ready.
我早就知道我还没准备好重新当一名警察
I knew I wasn't ready to go back to being police.
除了在大西洋城和克林顿城角落里的超市装袋以外
It's the only job I've ever had except for bagging groceries
当警察是我唯一做过的工作了
at the supermarket at the corner of Atlantic and Clinton.
我想我还是回去装袋去吧
I guess I could go back to that again.
"纸袋还是塑料袋呢"
"Paper or plastic?"
还掌握着这门技能呢
Yeah, still got it.
听我说 我也当过卧底
Listen to me, I was undercover.
和黑手党待了63天 我看到过很糟糕的事
63 days with the Mafia. I saw some messed-up stuff.
我知道你在挣扎什么
I know what your struggle is.
我能帮你从那段经历中恢复过来 但你必须要相信我
And I can bring you home, but you've got to trust me.
好 行
Okay. Yeah.
很好 现在我必须要睡一会儿
Great. Now, I've got to get some sleep.
如果你愿意的话 你可以留在这 办办案子
You're welcome to stay here and work the case if you want.
谢谢 搭档
Thanks, partner.
我保证一点都不会打扰到你
I promise I won't disturb you at all.
哼
Whuuuhhhh.
哈
- 嘿 Pimento  - 啊
- Hey, Pimento. - Huh?
我以为你就是看看文件什么的
I thought you were just gonna be looking through the files or something, man.
抱歉 兄弟
Sorry, brother.
太极能抑制心中的恶魔
Tai chi helps keep the demons at bay.
好吧
Right.
而且
And...
你非要穿着内裤打太极吗
Do you have to do it in your underwear?
我不能脱下来
I can't take them off,
因为那样的话你就会直直地看到我的丁丁和蛋蛋了
'cause then you'd be looking right at my penis and testicles.
这个逻辑倒是无法反驳 好吧
Can't argue with that logic. Mm-kay.
为什么这里有这么多垃圾
Why is there so much garbage in here?
刻薄Marge不想清理炖菜
Mean Marge won't clean up the stew.
而且还不给我们倒垃圾了
And also, she suspended our trash service.
发生啥了
What happened?
你还不够卑躬屈膝是吧
You didn't grovel enough, did you?
真的吗 Amy 你质疑我Charles Boyle
Seriously, Amy, you're gonna ask Charles Boyle
有没有足够卑躬屈膝  拜托
if he groveled enough? Come on!
这是我见过的最恶心的地方
This is the grossest thing I've ever seen,
而且我还有三个四岁以下的孩子呢
and I have three kids under the age of four.
我就住在鼻涕和口水里面
I live in a house of fluids.
听着 我有个计划
Look, I have a plan, okay?
我们就越过刻薄Marge
We're just gonna go over Mean Marge's head
直接告诉Holt
and we're gonna tell Holt.
告诉我什么
Tell me what?
噢 好吧 我不知道你有没有注意到
Oh, well, I don't know if you noticed,
昨天休息室发生了一场意外
but there was an accident in the break room yesterday.
噢 是的 碎玻璃和随处可见的骨头
Oh, yes, shattered windows, bones everywhere.
非常有70年代的纽约范儿 收拾干净
It's very "New York in the 70s." Clean it up.
问题是
The, uh, problem...
管理处的Marge拒绝帮助我们
is Marge in facilities is refusing to help.
我们希望你能和她谈一下
We were actually hoping maybe you could ask her.
什么
Excuse me?
我是这个片区的警监
I'm the captain of this precinct.
我没时间处理你们这些鸡毛蒜皮的小事
I don't have time to mediate your petty squabbles.
我发过神圣的誓要保护这个社区
I've taken a sacred oath to protect this community,
那才是需要我认真对待的工作
and that is a job I take seriously.
所以你也怕她是吗
So you're afraid of her, too, huh?
怕得不行
Terrified.
嗯 罪犯知道摄像头的位置
Yeah, perp knew where the camera was.
肯定之前就踩过点了
Must have cased the joint ahead of time.
我们需要你们过去一周的监控录像
We're gonna need all your footage from the past week.
哈哈哈 这太业余了
Ha-ha-ha. This is an amateur job.
所有人都知道你得在店主在的时候闯进来
Everybody knows you break in when the owner's there.
那样的话你就能确保能打开保险箱
That way you have guaranteed access to the safe,
而且你能踢掉他的牙以传达信息
and you can kick his teeth in to send a message.
好吧 为什么你不
Okay, why don't you just...
喔 没错 你能割了他的喉咙 但是接下来
Oh, sure, you could slit his throat,
你要怎么处理那些血呢
but then what are you going to do with all the blood?
额 我们就把血留在他的身体里 就是血液生活的地方
Uh, we'd leave it in his body, where blood lives,
因为我们是警察
because we're cops.
没错 我们是警察 不要担心 先生
Oh, right, we're cops. And don't worry, sir.
我们会抓住这些混蛋的
We're gonna catch these bastards,
- 要不然我就不叫Paul Sneed  - Adrian Pimento
- or my name isn't Paul Sneed. - Adrian Pimento.
Adrian Pimento 所以 他们拿走了什么
Adrian Pimento. So, what'd they take?
大约15000美元的东西
About $15,000 worth of stuff.
电视 相机 一些预付费的手机
TVs, cameras, bunch of pre-paid cell phones.
噢 你卖一次性电话吗
Ooh, you sell burner phones?
你卖的一次性电话有什么样的优惠套餐
What kind of deals you got on those?
你为什么想知道这些
Why do you want to know about the deals?
就是为了案件收集证据
Just gathering evidence for the case,
因为我是一名警察 记得吗
'cause I'm a cop, remember?
- Paul Sneed警探  - Adrian Pimento
- Detective Paul Sneed. - Adrian Pimento.
Adrian Piment  我知道我是谁 你知道吗 别管这些了
Adrian Piment--I--I know who I am--you know what--forget this!
啊 好吧
Ah--okay.
嘿 嘿 嘿 别这样 兄弟
Hey, hey, hey, come on, man.
听着 我懂 你还很紧张
Look, I get it... you're still tense.
当我从卧底任务中退出来的时候
When I came back from being undercover,
他们让我去看心理医生
they made me see a shrink.
然后他和我说我有恋父情结 然后我就说
But then he told me I had dad issues, and I was like,
"知道吗 你不能告诉我要做什么
"You know what, you can't tell me what to do,
你又不是我爹" 所以他是个白痴
you're not my dad," So he was a moron.
不 你知道吗 这建议真棒 谢谢朋友 谢谢你
No, you know what, that's good advice--thanks, man, thanks.
我 我马上就回来 我有东西落在里面了
I--I'll be right back, I just left something inside.
嘿 给我来一个
Hey, give me one of those.
为什么你要买一次性手机
Why are you buying a burner phone?
制烟机上
Cue smoke machine.
然后 开始 Holt出场
And...action Holt.
欢迎来到99片区 我是Raymond Holt警监
Welcome to the Nine-Nine. I'm Captain Raymond Holt.
我是Rosa Diaz警探
And I'm Detective Rosa Diaz.
我不知道我为什么要坐在轮椅上
I don't understand why I'm on a wheelchair.
卡
Cut!
我再说最后一遍 Rosa 通过特效
For the last time, Rosa, through the magic of special effects,
轮椅就会变成一匹马
the wheelchair will turn into a horse,
但我需要你配合我
but I need you to work with me.
给我几句 "驾" "驾"
Give me a little "Hee-yah!" Hee-yah!
这太蠢了
This is idiotic.
可能是因为你没有按剧本上说的一样
Maybe because you didn't karate chop your way
用空手道从烟里劈出一条路来
through the smoke, as scripted.
我不干了 Scully
I'm out. Scully.
Rosa
Rosa!
驾 驾
Hee-yah, hee-yah.
我想要一个简单明了的
I wanted a simple, straightforward
关于我们片区的视频介绍
video tour of the precinct,
而你加了一种我不喜欢的东西
and you've added the one ingredient I didn't want:
激情
pizzazz.
姐就是激情的代名词啊
Pizzazz is who I am.
你会让天空别那么蓝吗
Would you tell the sky to stop being so blue?
- 会 我希望天空是褐色  - 啥
- Yes. I wish it were tan. - What?
那是我最喜欢的颜色  我没有在胡说
It's my favorite color. It's no-nonsense.
嘿 我在跟踪Pimento
Hey, I've been tailing Pimento,
我觉得你说的是对的
and I think you were right.
他这人身上有些奇怪的地方
There's something weird going on with that guy.
我就知道 啊
I knew it. Ugh!
真不敢相信我要和他睡觉了
I can't believe I'm gonna sleep with him.
你可以不用这么做
Well, you don't have to.
不 我要
No, I'm gonna.
他偷偷地买了一次性电话
He secretly bought a burner phone,
他闯进了我的公寓
he broke into my apartment
而且他一直忘记他是个警察
and he keeps forgetting he's a cop
还叫他自己的化名 Paul Sneed
and calling himself by his alias, Paul Sneed.
Paul Sneed吗
Paul Sneed?
他说Figgis安插了间谍在纽约警局里面
He said Figgis has spies in the NYPD.
Rosa 万一他就是其中一个间谍怎么办 他叛变了怎么办
Rosa, what if he's one of them? What if he turned?
噢 他来了
Oh, here he comes.
天啊 断线钳
Oh, man, bolt cutters?
说真的 没有一个清白的人
Bolt cutters have literally
会用断线钳
never been used by an innocent person.
我做首饰的时候一直用断线钳啊
I use them all the time when I make jewelry.
啥 哦我的天啊
What? Oh, my God.
等下再跟进你这个问题
Follow-up questions later.
好了 我要继续跟踪他了
All right, I got to keep following him.
好 但是小心一点
All right, but be careful.
噢 别担心我 我会隐形的
Oh, don't worry about me. I'll be invisible.
现在你看到我了 现在你
Now you see me, now you--
我这边没事 没事
We're cool, we're cool.
一切正常 他没听到我 没事
Everything's still cool. He didn't hear me, we're cool.
Rosa
Rosa.
Pimento刚刚戴上了滑雪面罩
Pimento just put on a ski mask
然后潜进了一个吓人的废弃仓库里
and broke into a creepy abandoned warehouse.
嗯 这太性感了
Mm, that's hot.
是吗
It is?
噢 等下 他又出来了
Oh, wait, he's coming back out.
他有没有做什么特别可疑的事情
Did he do something super shady?
他的眼神是不是很狂野
Are his eyes all wild?
- Rosa 集中注意力  - 抱歉
- Rosa, focus. - Sorry.
发张照片来 拜拜
Send a pic. Bye.
好的 我猜我们聊完了
Okay, guess we're done talking.
他们还是没清理这里面
Well, they still haven't cleaned up in there,
但是好消息是我又有了一个新计划
but the good news is I got a new plan.
我会让一个罪犯意外地挣脱监管
I let one of the perps accidentally get out of holding,
然后我在休息室里抓住他
then I take him down to the break room.
天哪 现在这就变成了一个犯罪现场
Oopsie. Now it's a whole crime scene.
然后我们就能叫犯罪现场清理员了
And then we can get crime scene cleaners.
- 砰  - 别这么急
- Boom. - Not so fast.
我说清理那个屋子 那个屋子才能被清理
That room gets clean when I say it gets cleaned.
现在你阻止不了我们
You can't stop us now.
你听过那句谚语吗
You ever heard the old saying,
"从垃圾里就能了解一个人"
"Know the garbage, know the man?"
这根本就不是谚语
That's not a saying.
不 那就是 我知道你们全部的秘密
Yes, it is. I know all your secrets.
Boyle
Boyle.
你常吃快餐
You got a taste for fast food.
那些才不是我的呢
Those aren't mine.
我只吃本地产的肉
I only eat locally-sourced meats.
它们可能是Terry吃的 他以前很胖的 你知道吗
They could be Terry's. He was fat once, you know?
有没有搞错啊 Bolye
What the hell, Boyle?
说到Jeffords
Speaking of Jeffords,
也许你女儿会想知道
maybe your daughters would like to know
她们的爸爸把她们的画都给扔了
that their daddy throws away all their drawings?
她们画太多而且都不好看啊
They just draw so many, and they're all so bad.
还有你 Santiago
And you, Santiago,
也许我应该让大家看看你备忘录的草稿
maybe the world would like to see that draft of a memo you wrote
你把 there 拼成 their
where you used T-H-E-I-R instead of T-H-E-R-E?
你这个贱人
Oh, you sick son of a bitch.
为什么你这么恨我们
Why do you hate us so much?
我知道你们叫我刻薄Marge
I know you call me Mean Marge.
你们知道我姓什么吗
Do you even know my last name?
- "拖把桶"吗  - Scully 别猜了
- Mop-Bucket? - Scully, don't guess.
- 拜托了  - 别走
- Please. - No.
嘿嘿嘿大家别走啊
Guys, guys, guys, guys, guys.
"拖把桶" Scully你在逗我吗
"Mop-Bucket," Scully?
我的推测是有根据的
It was a educated guess.
谢谢你赶来
Thanks for coming.
Pimento把行李包放在后备箱里 把车停在角落就回家了
Pimento put the duffel in his trunk, parked around the corner,
然后他就一直光着身子打太极
and went home; he's been doing shirtless tai chi
就在窗户旁
in his window ever since.
哪个窗户
Which window is that?
- 嗯嗯  - 好吧
- Mm-hmm. - Okay.
听着 我得去查看一下那个后备箱
Look, I got to get into that trunk.
你需要我帮你把那辆车打开吗
And you need me to break into the car for you?
什么 不不不我可以的
What? No, I can do it.
你为什么这么说
Why would you say that?
因为有一次你丢了车钥匙 你竟然叫了辆拖车来
Because one time you lost your keys and you called a tow truck.
我妈会付道路救援的钱啊
My mom pays for roadside assistance.
为什么我不叫拖车 放着我来
Why wouldn't I call it? I'm doing this.
这次拍的很棒 你们终于掌握到诀窍了
Okay, great take! You guys are finally getting it.
我们再拍一条 开始 Holt出场
All right, let's go again. Action Holt!
欢迎来到九九片区 我是Raymond Holt警监
Welcome to the Nine-Nine. I'm Captain Raymond Holt.
我是Rosa Diaz警探
And I'm Detective Rosa Diaz. Hee-yah.
这都是什么啊
The hell is this?
你的表演没有活力 所以我们重新选角了 亲爱的
You had a pizzazz problem, so you've been recast, sweetie.
欢迎来到好莱坞
Welcome to Hollywood.
David和他的角色非常有共鸣
You know, David here really connected with the role.
秘诀就在为你的角色创造一个背景故事
The key is to invent a backstory for your character.
我演的Raymond Holt对药物上瘾 可是没人知道
Now, my Raymond Holt is addicted to pills, but no one knows.
你看吧 他真的很懂这些技巧
You see, he really understands the craft,
相比之下你和Rosa就有点糟糕
whereas you and Rosa just sort of flop around
就像一对无聊的普通人
like a couple of boring normals.
我很抱歉  但是我们是警探
I'm sorry, but we're detectives,
不是专业演员
not professional actors.
我们已经尽最大努力了
We were trying our hardest.
- "我们已经尽最大努力了"  - 别学我
- "We were trying our hardest." - Stop it.
Gina 这太不像话了 我决定不让你继续当导演了
Gina, this is a disgrace. I'm removing you as director.
他就这样走了
There he goes.
去嗑更多的药
Off to take more pills.
成功了
Oh, yeah.
再见了 道路救援
Suck it, roadside assistance.
唷唷唷
Well, well, well.
你好啊 Jake
Hello, Jake.
Adrian 这么巧我们居然偶遇了呢
Adrian, what a coincidence bumping into you here.
明天再见吧
Well, see you tomorrow.
嘿 不如我们逛逛吧
You know what, let's hang out now.
我也完全是这么想的呢
I was thinking the exact same thing.
搭档 你在这做什么呢
What are you doing here, partner?
Pimento还在窗户旁
Pimento's still in the window.
拜托 Jake
Come on, Jake.
你怎么都没猜到我会雇一个长得像我的人
You honestly didn't assume I would hire a look-alike
带着假胡子在我窗口打太极
to wear a fake beard and do tai chi in my window?
我真的百分百没猜到
No, I definitely didn't assume that.
还有 你不会真的觉得那是我吧
And plus, you seriously thought that was me?
你可是看过我穿内衣的样子啊
I mean, you've seen me in my underpants.
我的屁股完全是硬邦邦的
My butt is rock hard.
那个人的屁股松垮垮的
That guy's got a pancake butt.
我真不敢相信你还在为Figgis跑腿
I can't believe you're still working for Figgis.
所以你行为才这么奇怪
That's why you've been acting so weird.
闯进我的公寓 买一次性手机
Breaking into my apartment, buying a burner phone,
拿着这个行李包
grabbing this duffel.
我闯进你的公寓是因为在我家我感觉不安全
I broke into your apartment 'cause I didn't feel safe at my home.
好吧
Okay.
而且我只能买到一次性手机
And a burner phone is the only kind of phone I can get
因为我消失了12年
because I disappeared for 12 years,
- 现在我的信用特别差  - 有道理
- and now have terrible credit. - Makes sense.
你想知道这个行李包里有什么是吗
You want to know what's in the duffel?
打开啊 硬汉
Open it up, tough guy.
噢 看啊
Oh, look at that.
一堆的以前的家庭照片和个人物品呢
A bunch of old family photos and personal belongings.
Pimento的纪念品哦
Pimento's mementos.
我知道你正拿着枪指着我
I know you have a gun on me.
可是真的好押韵我忍不住 不好意思
I just couldn't resist the rhyme, sorry.
我成为Paul Sneed后就把这一切都藏起来了
I stashed it all when I became Paul Sneed.
我不能让他们找到任何这些东西
I couldn't have them finding anything
然后由此找到我的家人
that could trace back to my family.
我懂你的 好吗
I get it, all right?
我也经历了一样的事 当我回来的时候
I went through the exact same thing when I came back--
你根本不懂我经历了什么
You have no clue what I've been through!
你知道吗
You know what?
我真不敢相信我之前那么信任你
I can't believe I trusted you.
好吧
Okay.
你走吧 Jake
Just get out of here, Jake.
天哪 这个家伙的屁股松垮垮的
Oh, my God, this guy's got a pancake butt.
这不是Pimento 快离开那里 Jake
It's not Pimento. Get out of there, Jake!
多谢了 Rosa
Thanks, Rosa.
Pimento警探今天没来上班
So Detective Pimento didn't show up for work today.
你知道为什么吗
Any idea why?
噢是的 我把他赶走了
Oh, yeah, I straight up drove him off.
完全是我搞砸了
Big screw-up on my part.
我正在尝试这个新鲜事 承认自己的错误
I'm trying this new thing where I just own my mistakes.
- 我挺喜欢的 你呢  - 我本来也是
- I like it. Do you? - I did.
- 直到你开始炫耀  - 好吧
- Until you bragged about it. - Yeah.
Pimento把他的枪和警徽留在我桌上
Pimento left his gun and badge on my desk,
附着一张纸条说 "我做不了这个"
along with a note reading, "I can't do this.
我还是做打包员（收赃款的）更好
I'm better off as a bagman."
哦不
Oh, no.
你觉得他又回去给Figgis跑腿了吗
You think he went back to work with Figgis?
比这更糟
Worse.
行 都装在一个袋子里
Fine, single bag it.
明年的今天就是你的忌日 你这个贱人
It's your funeral, you dumb son of a bitch.
赶快滚吧
Get out of here.
白痴
Idiot.
嗨 搭档
Hey, partner.
打包员没有搭档
Bag boys don't have partners.
事实上 收银员和打包员
Actually, cashiers and bag boys
需要完全同步
need to be totally in sync--
闭嘴 Maggie
Shut up, Maggie.
兄弟 你把12年光阴都奉献给警察局
Look, man, you sacrificed 12 years of your life
你是个英雄
for the police department; you're a hero.
很抱歉我没有相信你
I'm sorry that I didn't trust you.
我也是
Yeah. Me too.
我可以告诉你一个我从没跟任何人说过的事吗
Look, can I tell you something I've never told anyone before?
我在黑手党做卧底的那段时间其实挺逊的
My time undercover in the Mafia was actually kind of lame.
我本想很狂拽酷炫的 但是
I mean, I wanted it to be badass, but
我对电脑在行 所以我基本上都在帮他们
I'm good at computers, so I mostly just helped them
换个邮箱什么的
switch over from AOL.
我不懂你都经历了什么
I have no idea what you're going through.
我想告诉你一切都会恢复正常的
And I want to tell you that it's all gonna go back to normal,
但说真的 我也不知道
but honestly, I have no clue.
无论如何 那个破门侵入的监控录像收到了
Anyways, the footage came back on that B&E,
我们有了一个嫌疑犯
and we've got a suspect.
我现在就要去搜捕他 你要一起来吗
I'm going to bust him right now if you want to come with me.
把那些鸡蛋给我吧
Why don't you give me those eggs?
我把它放在最上面
I'll put them on top here.
好吧
Okay.
什么事儿啊 你身上发生了什么
What was that about? What happened to you?
Maggie 少管闲事
Maggie, butt out!
好吗 这是我的生活
Okay? This is my life!
我刚刚收到消息
So I just received word
我在Guffin基金会的朋友说的
from our friend at the Guffin Foundation.
显然他们非常喜欢我们提交的视频
Apparently they loved our video submission.
你发送给他们什么了
What did you send them?
我发了一个银幕杰作
A cinematic masterpiece is what I sent them.
充满活力吗
Did it feature pizzazz?
不 完全不是 长官
No, none at all, sir.
一开始 我走了点弯路
First, I couldn't wrap my head around that concept,
然后我顿悟了
but then I realized:
你知道网上哪种狗狗会得到最多的赞吗
do you know which dogs get the most likes on the internet?
安纳托利亚牧羊犬
Anatolian Shepherds.
不 是发育不完全的丑丑的小矮狗
No, ugly little runts
眼神呆滞 舌头伸在嘴巴外面
with wonky eyes and tongues that won't stay in their mouths.
但是安纳托利亚牧羊犬
But the Anatolian Shepherd
在保护牲畜方面是无敌的
is unrivaled for protecting livestock.
我想要让他们惊艳到
I was trying to wow them,
那我应该向他们展示我们可怜的呆滞眼神
and I should have just been showcasing our wonk-eye.
我们已经尽最大的努力了 但这是我们的耻辱
We were trying our hardest, but this is a disgrace.
耻辱 耻辱
Disgrace, disgrace.
帮助我们 停止这一切
Help us. Stop it.
这是原本的音频 用的是你非常真实的崩溃时的声音
And that's real audio of your very-real diva meltdown.
看来你最终还是能成为一个杰出的演员的
You might just make it as an actor after all.
好样的Linetti
Well done, Linetti.
Linetti警长
Sergeant Linetti.
我让假Holt帮我升职了
I had the fake Holt give me a promotion.
他签署了文件还有一切手续
He signed the papers and everything.
你们想要干什么
What do you want?
我们来是想告诉你我们会正式把四楼休息室改名为
To tell you that we will officially be renaming
Marge Bronigan休息室
the fourth-floor break room "The Marge Bronigan Break Room."
好吧
Well.
看来有人做了功课
Looks like somebody did their homework.
是我 我做的
It was me. I did it.
那条件是什么
So what's the catch?
仪式在两小时后开始
The ceremony starts in two hours.
我知道我们小队不是清洁工工会成员
Now, I know our squad is not in the janitor's union,
但是如果能让我们在那之前帮你们
but it'd sure be nice if we were allowed
把那儿打扫干净 那就太好了
to clean the place up before then.
我们把炖羊肉都打扫干净了
We cleaned up the stew,
意味着Marge Bronigan休息室正式成立了
which means the Marge Bronigan Break Room is open for business!
好吧 我们会帮你们清理垃圾 做日常的清洁
Okay, we'll take out your trash, do normal cleaning,
但你们最好别弄出大乱子来
but no big messes.
太棒啦 命名典礼开始
Great! Time for the christening.
哦 糟了
Oh, crap.
恭喜啦
Congratulations.
嫌疑犯在三楼 每个人都知道自己的任务了吧
Perp is on the third floor. Everyone know your assignment?
介意我加入你们吗
Mind if I tag along?
Pimento
Pimento?
我考虑过了
I thought about it.
如果你说一切都会恢复正常
If you say things will get back to normal,
那我相信你
then I trust you.
好的 我们开始吧
All right.Let's do this.
你和我一起 搭档
You're with me Partner.
纽约警察局 你被捕了
NYPD. You'er under arrest.
你要死了
You'er gonna die.
不Pimento 不要啊
No,Pimento.No
电波字幕组 欢迎您的加入
官方网站:www.dbfansub.com
新浪微博:@电波字幕组